optionsbee.com 2017-12-21

# Privacy Policy

Your privacy is very important to us. Accordingly, we have developed this Policy in order for you to understand how we collect, use, communicate and disclose and make use of personal information. The following outlines OptionsBee privacy policy.   

  * Before or at the time of collecting personal information, we will identify the purposes for which information is being collected. 
  * We will collect and use of personal information solely with the objective of fulfilling those purposes specified by us and for other compatible purposes, unless we obtain the consent of the individual concerned or as required by law. 
  * We will only retain personal information as long as necessary for the fulfillment of those purposes. 
  * We will collect personal information by lawful and fair means and, where appropriate, with the knowledge or consent of the individual concerned. 
  * Personal data should be relevant to the purposes for which it is to be used, and, to the extent necessary for those purposes, should be accurate, complete, and up-to-date. 
  * We will protect personal information by reasonable security safeguards against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use or modification.

  * We will make readily available to customers information about our policies and practices relating to the management of personal information. We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles in order to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Cookies Usage Policy**

_Privacy Statement: How we use Cookies_

Cookies are very small text files that are stored on your computer when you visit some websites. 

We use cookies to help identify your computer so we can tailor your user experience.

The following are required to provide you with the best user experience and also to tell us which pages you find most interesting (anonymously).

Functional Cookies

This Website Will:

  * Track the pages you visits via Google Analytics. Click the following link for more information on how [Google uses cookies](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/technologies/cookies/).
  * Share your cookies with our advertising partners whenever you engage with ads that we display on our website.
  * Share your cookies with our affiliate partners in case you engage in any way with any of the affiliate programs that we endorse throughout our website.

Targeting Cookies

This Website Will:

  * Allow you to share pages with social networks such as Google+
  * Allow you to share pages via Add This

To view the ‘[Add This](http://www.addthis.com/privacy?utm_source=mf&utm_medium=link&utm_content=AT_privacy_MF15PC&utm_campaign=AT_privacy)’ Privacy Policy or to opt out of any online behavioural advertising, please visit Add This and click on the ‘Opt Out’ button.

This website will not:

Share any personal information with third parties.

If you have any questions regarding our Cookie Usage policy then please email us.

**_Back to Top_**
